Register of the Eric Voegelin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speaking Engagements and Trips File, 1958-1983
  Includes correspondence, itineraries, documents concerning travel arrangements, and outlines and typescripts of lectures. Dates listed refer to the date of the event; dates of documents within folders often span a year before and after the listed date, with documents containing discussions of travel arrangements and reactions to the event. Includes events involving the Intercollegiate Studies Institute.
  - University of Munich, inaugural lecture reactions, 1958 (Box-folder 124: 4)
    Inventory #415
  - Max Weber commemoration, "Die Grösse Max Webers,", 1964 (Box-folder 124: 5)
    Includes typescript of speech. Inventory #415
  - Deutsche Vereinigung für Politische Wissenschaft, Tutzing, Germany, "Was ist politische Realität?", 1965 (Box-folder 124: 6)
  - Harvard Divinity School, Ingersoll lecture on immortality, January 1965 (Box-folder 124: 7)
    Includes correspondence from 1966 to 1967. Inventory #415
  - Trip through English universities, Spring 1966 (Box-folder 124: 8)
    Sponsored by the British Council Munich. Inventory #412
  - University of Zagreb, "Die Situation der politischen Theorie in unserer Zeit,", October 1966 (Box-folder 124: 9)
  - Northwest University, 29 March 1968 (Box-folder 124: 10)
    Voegelin delivered a public lecture titled "The Pathology of Intellectual Movements" and a seminar lecture. Inventory #415
  - Stanford University, Committee on Public Exercises, 8 April 1969 (Box-folder 124: 11)
  - Dickinson College, Carlisle, Pennsylvania, 29 April and 1 May 1969 (Box-folder 124: 12)
  - East Texas State University, Commerce, Texas, 12-14 May 1969 (Box-folder 124: 13)
    Includes journal with "The Science and Demonology of Politics" by Ellis Sandoz. Inventory #415
  - Stanford University, Intercollegiate Studies Institute Western Summer Seminar, 17-23 August 1969 (Box-folder 125: 1)
  - Loyola University, New Orleans, Louisiana, "Aeschylus: Tragedy and the History of Humanity,", 6 October 1969 (Box-folder 125: 2)
  - Reed College, Portland, Oregon, November 1969 (Box-folder 125: 3)
  - Expense reports, 1969-1973
    Includes correspondence and receipts. Inventory #412
    - Europe trip of August to September 1969 (Box-folder 125: 4)
    - Europe and Canada trip of October to November 1970 (Box-folder 125: 5)
    - Mexico trip of May 1971 (Box-folder 125: 6)
    - Europe and Near East trip, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 125: 7)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute summer seminary with director Charles Heatherly, 1970 (Box-folder 125: 8)
  - Europe and Canada trip, Fall 1970 (Box-folder 125: 9)
    Includes correspondence and itineraries. Inventory #412
  - Sir George Williams University, January 1970 (Box-folder 125: 10)
  - University of Dallas, Braniff Graduate School, 26 February 1970 (Box-folder 125: 11)
  - Pittsburgh Theological Seminary, April 1970 (Box-folder 125: 12)
  - University of Massachusetts, Amherst, "Common Sense Revolution and Apocalypse,", 13 April 1970 (Box-folder 126: 1)
  - American Political Science Association, Los Angeles, Conference for Democratic Politics, 8-9 September 1970 (Box-folder 126: 2)
    Voegelin cancelled his appearance at this event. Inventory #415
  - Loyola College of Montreal, November 1970 (Box-folder 126: 3)
  - University of Ottawa, November 1970 (Box-folder 126: 4)
  - Annual trip of 1971 (Malta, Athens, Munich, and Paris) (Box-folder 126: 5)
  - Notre Dame University, 1971 (Box-folder 126: 6)
    Bills from the Morris Inn. Inventory #412
  - Trip to Yucatan, Mexico City, and Rome, 1971 (Box-folder 126: 7)
    Bills from the Morris Inn. Inventory #414
  - Hillsdale College, Michigan, Center for Constructive Alternatives, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 126: 8)
    Voegelin did not attend this event. Inventory #412
  - Posters and flyers advertising Voegelin's lectures, 1971-1972, undated (Box-folder 126: 9)
    Inventory #256
  - University of Michigan, lecture, 22 March 1971 (Box-folder 126: 10)
    Inventory #414
  - American Academy in Rome, 1-3 April 1971 (Box-folder 126: 11)
    Includes typescript of "On Classical Studies." Inventory #414
  - Notre Dame University, "The School of Eric Voegelin" symposium, 29-30 April 1971 (Box-folder 126: 12)
    Includes papers on Voegelin's works. Inventory #414
  - Duke University, 2-4 May 1971 (Box-folder 126: 13)
  - Seattle, Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 19 May 1971 (Box-folder 126: 14)
  - Stanford University, Intercollegiate Studies Institute summer school, 22-28 August 1971 (Box-folder 126: 15)
  - American Political Science Association, "An Evening with Eric Voegelin,", 10 September 1971 (Box-folder 126: 16)
  - Louisiana State University, 29 November and 2 December 1971 (Box-folder 126: 17)
  - Philadelphia Society, western regional meeting, 3-4 December 1971 (Box-folder 126: 18)
  - Annual trip of 1972 (Ireland) (Box-folder 126: 19)
  - Hartford Seminary Foundation, seminar on Gnosticism, 17-18 March 1972 (Box-folder 126: 20)
  - City University of New York, 31 March 1972 (Box-folder 127: 1)
    Includes lecture outline. Inventory #414
  - East Texas State University, 3 May 1972 (Box-folder 127: 2)
  - Stanford University, Intercollegiate Studies Institute summer conference, 27 August-2 September 1972 (Box-folder 127: 3)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 29 October-1 November 1972 (Box-folder 127: 4)
  - Annual trip of 1973 (Iran and Turkey) (Box-folder 127: 5)
  - Travel receipts from, 1973 (Box-folder 127: 6)
  - Villanova University, Intercollegiate Studies Institute, The Decline of Authority in Western Civilization seminar, 10 March 1973 (Box-folder 127: 7)
    Includes typescript of lecture. Inventory #413
  - Stanford University, Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 19-25 August 1973 (Box-folder 127: 8)
    Includes correspondence with Charles Heatherly. Inventory #413
  - Switzerland, Institute for Intercultural Research Colloquium, 23-30 September 1973 (Box-folder 127: 9-11)
  - Dominican College of San Rafael, Symposium in the Humanities, 10 November 1973 (Box-folder 127: 12)
    Voegelin did not attend this event. Inventory #413
  - Expense reports and receipts for speaking engagements in, 1974 (Box-folder 127: 13)
  - University of Southern California, School of Public Administration Seminar, 9 January 1974 (Box-folder 127: 14)
  - Earlham College, 10-12 April 1074 (Box-folder 128: 1)
  - Loyola University of Chicago, 24 April 1974 (Box-folder 128: 2)
  - University of Florida, Gainesville, 6-8 May 1974 (Box-folder 128: 3)
  - Pepperdine University, Intercollegiate Studies Institute summer school, 19-23 August 1974 (Box-folder 128: 4)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Santa Barbara, California, 6 September 1974 (Box-folder 128: 5)
  - Trip to Japan, Germany, and Taiwan, September 1974 (Box-folder 128: 6)
  - Malibu Authors Society, 12 September 1974 (Box-folder 128: 7)
  - Conference of the Society for Intercultural Cooperation, Kyoto, Japan, 27 September 1974 (Box-folder 128: 8)
  - American Academy of Religion, 24-27 October 1974 (Box-folder 128: 9)
  - University of Virginia, 28 October 1974 (Box-folder 128: 10)
  - University of Washington, visit in, 1975 (Box-folder 128: 11)
    Includes correspondence from 1974 with Eugene Webb. Inventory #413
  - Purdue University lectures, 16 January 1975 (Box-folder 128: 12)
    Inventory #376
  - University Center in Virginia, March 1975 (Box-folder 128: 13)
    Inventory #374
  - Philadelphia Society annual meeting, 18-19 April 1975 (Box-folder 128: 14)
    Inventory #375
  - East Texas State University, November 1975 (Box-folder 128: 15)
    Inventory #369
  - Trips, 1976 (Box-folder 128: 16)
  - University of Southern California, colloquium on the ethics of experience and behavior control, 12-14 February 1976 (Box-folder 128: 17)
    Includes letter to Henry Clark on behaviorism and discourse with ideologists. Inventory #386
  - Thomas More Institute for Adult Education, Montreal lecture, March 1976 (Box-folder 128: 18)
    Includes letter to Henry Clark on behaviorism and discourse with ideologists. Inventory #385
  - University of Washington, 3-4 March 1976 (Box-folder 128: 19)
    Voegelin gave two lectures titled "Religious Experience and Dogmatism in the Ancient World" and "Religious Experience and Dogmatism in the Modern World." Inventory #387
  - International Society for Comparative Study of Civilizations annual meeting, 1-4 April 1976 (Box-folder 128: 20)
    Inventory #384
  - Philadelphia Society national meeting, 9-10 April 1976 (Box-folder 128: 21)
    Includes correspondence about appointing Voegelin as a distinguished member. Inventory #383
  - Santa Barbara City College, Continuing Education Division, "Transformation of Culture" lecture series, May 1976 (Box-folder 128: 22)
    Also sponsored by the Institute for Higher Studies and the Museum of Natural History. Includes typescript of "International Law" by Harvey Wheeler. Inventory #382
  - International Society for the Study of Time Conference, 1-10 July 1976 (Box-folder 128: 23)
  - American Political Science Association meeting, 2-5 September 1976 (Box-folder 129: 1)
    Inventory #381
  - Virginia trip, October 1976 (Box-folder 129: 2)
  - University of California, Berkeley, "The Problem of Reality" lecture, 22 November 1976 (Box-folder 129: 3)
    Inventory #379
  - Philadelphia Society regional meeting in Dallas, 4 December 1976 (Box-folder 129: 4)
    Inventory #380
  - Hillsdale College, Michigan, "Between Nothingness and Paradise: Faith,", 13-18 February 1977 (Box-folder 129: 5)
    Inventory #392
  - University of Notre Dame, Orestes Brownson Society, "The Apocalypse of Abraham" lecture, 25 February 1977 (Box-folder 129: 6)
  - University of Notre Dame, "The Truth of Reason and the Truth of Vision" lecture, 25-28 April 1977 (Box-folder 129: 7)
    Inventory #391
  - University of Virginia, September 1977 (Box-folder 129: 8)
    Includes "Statement on the Political and Social Thought Program" typescript. Inventory #390
  - Thomas More Institute, symposium on adult learning, 23-24 September 1977 (Box-folder 129: 9)
    Inventory #389
  - Syracuse University, "The Truth of Reason," "The Truth of Vision," "The Beginning and the Beyond" lectures, 31 October-2 November 1977 (Box-folder 129: 10)
    Inventory #388
  - Jerusalem trip, 11-26 October 1983 (Box-folder 129: 11)
- Incremental Office File, 1978-1979
  Includes clippings, correspondence, course listings, and faculty listings related to the Geschwister-Scholl-Institut für Politische Wissenschaft (Universität München). Arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Clippings announcing Jubilee, 1978 (Box-folder 129: 12)
    Inventory #250c
  - Correspondence, Peter C. Mayer-Tasch, 1978 (Box-folder 129: 13)
    Inventory #250a
  - Course and faculty listings, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 129: 14)
    Inventory #250b
- Incremental Subject File, circa 1936-1987
  Includes artist exhibit books, catalogs, clippings, invitations, and archaeological maps. Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Archaeology: Malta, Java, India, Newgrange, undated (Box-folder 129: 15)
    Includes maps. See also Photographs and postcards. Inventory #257
  - Artist exhibits, 1967-1976, undated (Box-folder 129: 16)
    Inventory #261
  - Corpus Christi College catalogue of manuscripts, undated (Box-folder 129: 17)
    Inventory #258
  - Gesellschaft für Auslandskunde, 1987 (Box-folder 129: 18)
    Invitation to see speaker George Stanley McGovern. Inventory #204
  - Miscellany, 1975, undated (Box-folder 129: 19)
  - Wien: Kulturgeschichte einer Stadt von den Römerzeiten bis zur Gegenwart, book catalog, circa 1936 (Box-folder 129: 20)
    Inventory #441
- Lissy Voegelin File, 1924-1992
  Includes appointment books, biographical documents and correspondence of Lissy Voegelin, also known as Luise Betty Voegelin, wife of Eric Voegelin. Arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Address books, undated (Box-folder 130: 1-3)
    Inventory #431e
  - Addresses, undated (Box-folder 130: 4)
    Inventory #265
  - Appointment books and calendars
    - 1968 (Box-folder 130: 5)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 130: 6)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 130: 7)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 130: 8)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 130: 9)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 130: 10)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 131: 1)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 131: 2)
    - 1976 (Box-folder 131: 3)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 131: 4)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 131: 5)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 131: 6)
  - Baptismal record of Lissy Voegelin, excerpt from the day book of the Evangelical Reform Church in Vienna, 1924 (Box-folder 131: 7)
    Record for baptism in 1906. Originally filed with naturalization and immigration documents (Box 107, Folders 1-2). Inventory #275.
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 131: 8)
      Includes letters from Margaret Fisher Dalrymple, Michael Pinkston, L. E. Phillabaum, and Charlie W. Roberts. Inventory #310
    - Fragment, undated (Box-folder 131: 9)
      Inventory #254g
    - "An Goethe,", 1949-1988, undated (Box-folder 131: 10)
      Inventory #267
    - Baruzzi, Renate, 1965 (Box-folder 131: 11)
      Inventory #254f
    - Dulles, Mrs. (The Morris Inn, Notre Dame), 1968 (Box-folder 131: 12)
      Inventory #254c
    - Duso, Giuseppe ( Filosofia Politica), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 131: 13)
      Inventory #207
    - Henningsen, Manfred, 1967 (Box-folder 131: 14)
      Inventory #254d
    - Opitz, Paul and [Otto] Schulmeister, 1989, undated (Box-folder 131: 15)
      Inventory #266
    - Schulmeister, Otto ( Die Presse), 1988 (Box-folder 131: 16)
      Inventory #206
  - Naturalization documents. See Incremental biographical file (Box 107, Folders 1-2)
  - Passports, circa 1973-1983 (Box-folder 131: 17)
    Inventory #431
- Writings by Others, 1977-1984
  Printed copies of writings, including several works that are inscribed to Eric Voegelin. Arranged alphabetically by author.
  - Brun, Jean, "Zum Problem der Säkularisierung,", 1977 (Box-folder 131: 18)
    Inscribed. Inventory #400
  - De Grazia, Sebastian, "Hat and Cup in Hand: Political Pliancy and the Loss of Leisure in Universities,", circa 1979 (Box-folder 131: 19)
    Inventory #401
  - Heilman, Robert B., "RPW at LSU: Some Reminiscences" (Robert Penn Warren at Louisiana State University), 1981 (Box-folder 131: 20)
    Inscribed. Inventory #398
  - Jaffé, George, "Paula Hegner's Musikalischer Werdegang,", undated (Box-folder 131: 21)
    Inventory #254i
  - Leclerc, Ivor, "The Ontology of Descartes,", 1980 (Box-folder 131: 22)
    Inventory #397
  - McEvoy, James, "Sapientiae Doctrina,", 1980 (Box-folder 131: 23)
    Inscribed. Inventory #399
  - Maurer, Reinhart, "Thesen zur politischen Theologie,", 1982 (Box-folder 131: 24)
    Inventory #404
  - Mehta, Vrajendra Raj, Beyond Marxism: Towards an Alternative Perspective, 1978, undated (Box-folder 132: 1)
    Includes letter to Voegelin from author. Inscribed. Inventory #394
  - Sedlmayr, Hans, "Ästhetischer Anarchismus in Romantik und Moderne,", 1978 (Box-folder 132: 2)
    Inscribed. Inventory #403
  - Slover, George, "Magic, Mystery, and Make-believe: An Analogical Reading of The Tempest," Shakespeare Studies, undated (Box-folder 132: 3)
    Inscribed. Inventory #395
  - Tejera, V., "Plato's Politicus," parts 1 and 2 of Why Plato Wrote Dialogues, circa 1979 (Box-folder 132: 4)
    Includes letter to Voegelin from author. Inventory #402
  - Tellenbach, Hubertus, "Wähnen, Wahn und Wahnsinn in Sophokles' Oidipus Tyrannos,", 1980 (Box-folder 132: 5)
    Inscribed. Inventory #396
  - Vondung, Klaus, "Träume von Tod und Untergang" and "Was heisst hier eigentlich "Apokalyptisch?", 1984, undated (Box-folder 132: 6)
    Inventory #405
- Photographs and Postcards, 1920s-1981, undated
  Scope and Contents Note
  Includes prints, negatives, and postcards with images of scenic views, cityscapes, and artifacts.
  - Photographs
    Includes 19 prints in 5 envelopes
    - 2 passport photos, 1948 and 1963; and 1 print of Eric Voegelin in August 1966 (Envelope A)
    - 4 prints of Eric Voegelin and other participants of a conference organized by the Institut für Politische Wissenschaft in Salzburg, Austria, August 2, 1962 (Envelope B)
    - 1 print of Eric Voegelin speaking at a conference organized by the Istituto Accademico di Roma in Rome, Italy, October 4, 1968 (Envelope C)
    - 9 prints of Eric Voegelin at the University of Augsburg, West Germany, upon receiving an honorary degree, May 13, 1981 (Envelope D)
    - 2 prints of Eric Voegelin in Munich, West Germany, upon receiving the city's gold medal "München leuchtet - Den Freund Münchens,", May 20, 1981 (Envelope E)
  - Incremental photographs
    - Marie König, archaeological photographs, circa 1969 (Box-folder 132: 7)
      Titled "France and elsewhere." Inventory #407c
    - Reformation figures, 1930s-1960s (Box-folder 132: 8)
      Includes prints, negatives, and notes. Inventory #259
  - Photo albums
    Includes prints and postcards of artifacts.
    - Archaeological artifacts, undated (Box-folder 132: 9-10)
      Includes photographs and postcard of the Hagia Sophia. Inventory #407b
    - Borobudur, undated (Box-folder 132: 11)
      Monument in Indonesia. Photographs sent to Voegelin by Ambassador Howard P. Jones. Inventory #408D
    - Ireland, undated (Box-folder 132: 12, Box-folder 133: 1)
      Includes photographs of artifacts such as early Christian slabs in Clonmacnoise, St. Brigid's crosses, and high crosses. Includes some photographs of paintings and artifacts from miscellaneous areas. See also Newgrange (Box 133, Folder 4). Inventory #407a
    - Malta and Greece, undated (Box-folder 133: 2-3)
      Inventory #408b
    - Newgrange, undated (Box-folder 133: 4)
      Monument in Ireland. Includes images of Knowth. Inventory #408a
    - Persepolis, Iran, and California, undated (Box-folder 133: 5-6)
      Includes essay by Douglas Mazonowicz. Inventory #408c
  - Postcards, 1920s, undated (Box 134)
    Majority of postcards do not contain writing, except for some to Eric or Lissy Voegelin, including a postcard sent from Gilbert Weiss. Includes images of monuments and landscapes in Iran, Rome, United States (including Yellowstone National Park), London, Spain (including Seville), France, and other countries; paintings and drawings; and buildings and portraits. Inventory #432
  - Negatives and prints, circa 1920s
    Includes scenic views of Yellowstone National Park, Niagara Falls, Stanford University, Vienna, and various cities in the United States. Negatives of exterior architecture often contain images of churches. Locations of images found in negatives possibly correspond with cities where postcards in the collection were purchased. Arranged alphabetically within original packets.
    - Packet 1, negatives
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 1-7)
        Possibly including images of the University of Vienna
      - Architecture, interior (Box-folder 135: 8-11)
      - Bison in a field (Box-folder 135: 12-13)
      - Cityscape (Box-folder 135: 14-19)
      - City scene (Box-folder 135: 20)
      - Fenced in ostriches (Box-folder 135: 21-24)
      - Forest scene with a bear (Box-folder 135: 25)
      - Geyser (?) (Box-folder 135: 26)
      - Landscapes (Box-folder 135: 27-100)
        Possibly including images of the Grand Canyon
      - Man in suit sitting on fallen trees (Box-folder 135: 101)
      - Men standing near hills (Box-folder 135: 102)
      - Palm trees (Box-folder 135: 103-106)
      - Palm trees and stage (Box-folder 135: 107)
      - People at the beach (Box-folder 135: 108)
      - People by a body of water (Box-folder 135: 109)
      - People on a mountain road (Box-folder 135: 110)
      - People sitting on benches (Box-folder 135: 111)
      - People sitting on benches by a pavilion (Box-folder 135: 112-113)
      - People standing beside cars (Box-folder 135: 114)
      - Photographer with an animal (Box-folder 135: 115)
      - Portrait of a man (Box-folder 135: 116)
      - Stanford campus (Box-folder 135: 117-123)
      - Street parade, possibly in Vienna (Box-folder 135: 124-125)
      - Street scene (Box-folder 135: 126-128)
      - Women standing near a geyser (Box-folder 135: 129)
    - Packet 2, negatives
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 130-139)
      - Dock/marina (Box-folder 135: 140-141)
      - Landscape (Box-folder 135: 142-155)
      - Landscape with buildings (Box-folder 135: 156-159)
      - Man on horseback (Box-folder 135: 160)
      - Street scene (Box-folder 135: 161-164)
    - Packet 3, negatives
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 165-172)
      - Architecture, interior (Box-folder 135: 173-176)
      - Landscape with buildings (Box-folder 135: 177)
    - Packet 4, prints
      - Four prints of architecture found in packets 3 and 5 (Box-folder 135: 178)
    - Packet 5, negatives
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 179-183)
      - Architecture, interior (Box-folder 135: 184)
    - Packet 6, negatives
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 185-195)
      - Women sitting on a bench (Box-folder 135: 196-197)
    - Packet 7, negatives and prints
      - Negatives
        - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 198-207)
          Includes images of a skyscraper
        - Cityscape (Box-folder 135: 208-210)
        - City scene (Box-folder 135: 211-213)
      - Prints
        - Three prints of ships and children with toy boats (Box-folder 135: 214)
    - Packet 8, negatives
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 215-219)
      - Architecture, interior (Box-folder 135: 220-224)
      - Building under construction (Box-folder 135: 225)
      - Cityscape (Box-folder 135: 226)
      - Docks and boats (Box-folder 135: 227)
      - Gravestones (Box-folder 135: 228-230)
      - Lake/riverside scene (Box-folder 135: 231)
      - Landscape (Box-folder 135: 232-248)
      - Man standing by a tree (Box-folder 135: 249)
      - Man standing in a field (Box-folder 135: 250)
      - On deck of a ship (Box-folder 135: 251)
      - People having a picnic (Box-folder 135: 252)
      - People sitting under a tree (Box-folder 135: 253)
      - People standing in a field (Box-folder 135: 254-255)
      - Ships on the water (Box-folder 135: 256-257)
      - Stanford campus (Box-folder 135: 258)
      - Street scene (Box-folder 135: 259)
    - Packet 9, negatives
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 260-271)
      - Architecture, interior (staircase) (Box-folder 135: 272-273)
      - Cityscape (Box-folder 135: 274-287)
      - Four men by car (Box-folder 135: 288-289)
      - Landscape (Box-folder 135: 290-303)
        Includes images of Niagara Falls
      - Man against a landscape (Box-folder 135: 304)
      - Man in front of tall building (Box-folder 135: 305)
        Image of the same building found in second architecture, exterior negative
      - Man leaning against wall (Box-folder 135: 306)
      - Man sitting beside a tree (Box-folder 135: 307)
      - Second man sitting beside a tree (Box-folder 135: 308)
      - Man standing by a columned railing (Box-folder 135: 309)
      - Park scene (Box-folder 135: 310-313)
      - People crossing a street near a set (Box-folder 135: 314)
      - People standing by a cliff (Box-folder 135: 315)
      - Ship docked (Box-folder 135: 316)
      - Street scene (Box-folder 135: 317-340)
    - Packet 10, negatives
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 341-346)
      - Architecture, interior (Box-folder 135: 347)
      - Landscape (Box-folder 135: 348-352)
    - Packet 11, negatives
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 353-376)
      - Architecture, exterior (Box-folder 135: 377-378)
        Originally housed in inner sleeve of envelope
      - Architecture, interior (Box-folder 135: 379-380)
      - People standing near a cathedral (Box-folder 135: 381)